hello and welcome to highbeast tv this
is chetan yamada icici lombard india's
leading private general insurance
company has appointed sheena kapoor as
its new head marketing corporate
communications and csr in this role
sheena will focus on developing and
strengthening corporate advertising and
branding customer oriented awareness
strategies across all company product
lines and geographies she will spearhead
the company's innovative efforts with an
enterprise-wide focus thereby aiding in
scaling the company's overall brand
positioning among other players
sheena kapoor brings with her over two
decades experience in the field of
marketing and corporate communications
speaking on the appointment jerry joe's
head human resources icsa lombard
general insurance said we are delighted
to welcome sheena into the icici lombard
family her experience will be
instrumental in combining consumer
insights analytics and innovation to
develop sharp branding and communication
thereby making her the perfect fit to
take the brand awareness to the next
level commenting on her appointment
sheena kapoor said with a wider remit
than ever before the industry needs to
cultivate a deeper connection with new
age customers today i am thrilled to
accept this new role and look forward to
being a part of brand whose ethos serves
to make insurance convenient transparent
and easily accessible for its customers
thank you for watching high business
you